{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -7451.51 - -1709.92 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-7451.51 - -1709.92 = -7451.51 + 1709.92 = -5741.59"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -1337.47 + 5068.04 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-1337.47 + 5068.04 = 3730.57"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -6211.70 * -6871.61 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-6211.70 * -6871.61 = 6211.70 * 6871.61 = 42684380.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -3985.41 - -8173.86 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-3985.41 - -8173.86 = -3985.41 + 8173.86 = 4188.45"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 1075.16 - 8090.56 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "1075.16 - 8090.56 = -7015.4"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -9299.25 * 1012.66 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-9299.25 * 1012.66 = -9416979.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -2864.35 - -8690.01 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-2864.35 - -8690.01 = -2864.35 + 8690.01 = 5825.66"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 7310.69 + -6470.86 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "7310.69 + -6470.86 = 839.83"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -3476.06 + 2490.05 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-3476.06 + 2490.05 = -986.01"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n商品原价为 19 元，打折后的价格为 71 元，请计算打折的折扣比例。\n\n### Response:", "solution": "= (19 - 71) / 19 * 100\n= -52 / 19 * 100\n= -2.7368 * 100\n= -273.68"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 1647.72 * -2175.26 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "1647.72 * -2175.26 = -3584219.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n解方程 -13x + 10 = 0\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-13x = -10.0\nx = -10.0 / -13\nx = 0.77\n方程的解为：0.77"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -1980.46 - -4548.03 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-1980.46 - -4548.03 = -1980.46 + 4548.03 = 2567.57"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -9349.89 + 8736.20 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-9349.89 + 8736.20 = -613.69"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -7881.79 + -3132.78 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-7881.79 + -3132.78 = -11014.57"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 7374.53 * -4084.42 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "7374.53 * -4084.42 = -30120678.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 6811.55 - 2494.54 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "6811.55 - 2494.54 = 4317.01"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 6974.95 的平方根？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "√6974.95 = 83.52"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -3957.83 - 3083.39 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-3957.83 - 3083.39 = -7041.22"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 8230.71 - 2598.23 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "8230.71 - 2598.23 = 5632.48"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n解方程 53x + 27 = 0\n\n### Response:", "solution": "53x = -27.0\nx = -27.0 / 53\nx = -0.51\n方程的解为：-0.51"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 2670.86 / 8327.57 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "2670.86 / 8327.57 = 0.32"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -1295.35 + 7059.64 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-1295.35 + 7059.64 = 5764.29"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 5113.34 - 239.46 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "5113.34 - 239.46 = 4873.88"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 4157.45 的平方根？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "√4157.45 = 64.48"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -8141.51 - -9883.79 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-8141.51 - -9883.79 = -8141.51 + 9883.79 = 1742.28"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 3619.12 + -4630.69 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "3619.12 + -4630.69 = -1011.57"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n商品原价为 50 元，打折后的价格为 42 元，请计算打折的折扣比例。\n\n### Response:", "solution": "= (50 - 42) / 50 * 100\n= 8 / 50 * 100\n= 0.16 * 100\n= 16.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -337.33 的 2 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-337.33^2 = 113791.53"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n商品原价为 56 元，打折后的价格为 20 元，请计算打折的折扣比例。\n\n### Response:", "solution": "= (56 - 20) / 56 * 100\n= 36 / 56 * 100\n= 0.6429 * 100\n= 64.29"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n解方程 -5x + -100 = 0\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-5x = 100.0\nx = 100.0 / -5\nx = -20.0\n方程的解为：-20.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 8115.42 / -8891.52 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "8115.42 / -8891.52 = -0.91"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 4670.73 + 5116.49 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "4670.73 + 5116.49 = 9787.22"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 2921.61 - -426.91 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "2921.61 - -426.91 = 2921.61 + 426.91 = 3348.52"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n商品原价为 47 元，打折后的价格为 12 元，请计算打折的折扣比例。\n\n### Response:", "solution": "= (47 - 12) / 47 * 100\n= 35 / 47 * 100\n= 0.7447 * 100\n= 74.47"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 4023.23 + -4657.63 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "4023.23 + -4657.63 = -634.4"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 6365.40 的平方根？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "√6365.40 = 79.78"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -6402.63 + 9129.29 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-6402.63 + 9129.29 = 2726.66"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 8049.63 的平方根？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "√8049.63 = 89.72"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 8874.39 / -5271.14 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "8874.39 / -5271.14 = -1.68"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -721.97 的 1 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-721.97^1 = -721.97"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n解方程 -33x + 79 = 0\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-33x = -79.0\nx = -79.0 / -33\nx = 2.39\n方程的解为：2.39"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 5396.67 + -7513.38 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "5396.67 + -7513.38 = -2116.71"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -5555.48 - 2227.05 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-5555.48 - 2227.05 = -7782.53"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 3585.58 * -7185.14 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "3585.58 * -7185.14 = -25762894.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 8326.91 + 8323.56 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "8326.91 + 8323.56 = 16650.47"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 6412.43 + 8195.96 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "6412.43 + 8195.96 = 14608.39"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n一个长方形的长为 48 厘米，宽为 7 厘米，请计算其面积。\n\n### Response:", "solution": "48 * 7 = 336\n面积为 336 平方厘米"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -2068.77 + -1347.07 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-2068.77 + -1347.07 = -3415.84"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n当 x = 0.64 时，求函数 y = 93x^80 的值\n\n### Response:", "solution": "y = 93*0.64^80\ny = 93*0.0\ny = 0.0\n函数的值为：0.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n解方程 -44x + 70 = 0\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-44x = -70.0\nx = -70.0 / -44\nx = 1.59\n方程的解为：1.59"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -5351.95 + -9780.91 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-5351.95 + -9780.91 = -15132.86"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 6585.23 * -469.39 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "6585.23 * -469.39 = -3091041.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 5591.19 / -7097.76 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "5591.19 / -7097.76 = -0.79"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 2910.65 * -4198.96 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "2910.65 * -4198.96 = -12221703.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -5861.56 - -6927.43 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-5861.56 - -6927.43 = -5861.56 + 6927.43 = 1065.87"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -5452.84 / -2723.07 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-5452.84 / -2723.07 = 5452.84 / 2723.07 = 2.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 8508.06 / 4921.11 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "8508.06 / 4921.11 = 1.73"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -3859.13 + 8440.41 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-3859.13 + 8440.41 = 4581.28"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -6983.88 - -8060.14 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-6983.88 - -8060.14 = -6983.88 + 8060.14 = 1076.26"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n求以下数据的平均值：[17, 99, 52]\n\n### Response:", "solution": "17 + 99 + 52 = 168\n168 / 3 = 56.0\n平均值为: 56.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 680.12 的 3 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "680.12^3 = 314598493.38"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n解方程 -97x + -92 = 0\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-97x = 92.0\nx = 92.0 / -97\nx = -0.95\n方程的解为：-0.95"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 123.84 的 1 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "123.84^1 = 123.84"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 5708.06 的平方根？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "√5708.06 = 75.55"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -7194.48 * -6220.64 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-7194.48 * -6220.64 = 7194.48 * 6220.64 = 44754270.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 8830.69 * -1065.17 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "8830.69 * -1065.17 = -9406186.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 1855.82 - 1345.12 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "1855.82 - 1345.12 = 510.7"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 8.74 * -9037.79 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "8.74 * -9037.79 = -78990.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -3321.89 * -3531.67 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-3321.89 * -3531.67 = 3321.89 * 3531.67 = 11731819.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 3460.04 - -315.20 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "3460.04 - -315.20 = 3460.04 + 315.20 = 3775.24"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 6185.13 - 2193.41 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "6185.13 - 2193.41 = 3991.72"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -5208.71 / 3443.94 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-5208.71 / 3443.94 = -1.51"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 1432.15 + -7448.73 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "1432.15 + -7448.73 = -6016.58"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -7375.26 * -8346.62 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-7375.26 * -8346.62 = 7375.26 * 8346.62 = 61558493.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -1552.54 / 6004.21 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-1552.54 / 6004.21 = -0.26"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -2508.22 / -8899.74 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-2508.22 / -8899.74 = 2508.22 / 8899.74 = 0.28"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -3459.21 * 4229.30 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-3459.21 * 4229.30 = -14630037.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n求以下数据的平均值：[71, 54, 62, 70, 53]\n\n### Response:", "solution": "71 + 54 + 62 + 70 + 53 = 310\n310 / 5 = 62.0\n平均值为: 62.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -368.19 的 4 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-368.19^4 = 18377564503.26"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -9245.32 * 2915.01 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-9245.32 * 2915.01 = -26950200.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 3362.63 * 7545.83 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "3362.63 * 7545.83 = 25373834.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -514.60 / 293.74 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-514.60 / 293.74 = -1.75"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n解方程 -80x + 94 = 0\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-80x = -94.0\nx = -94.0 / -80\nx = 1.18\n方程的解为：1.18"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -3279.11 - 7172.93 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-3279.11 - 7172.93 = -10452.04"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -9247.11 - 7331.30 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-9247.11 - 7331.30 = -16578.41"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -1738.37 + 4806.48 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-1738.37 + 4806.48 = 3068.11"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 10.63 的 2 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "10.63^2 = 113.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -7735.89 + 3030.00 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-7735.89 + 3030.00 = -4705.89"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -1058.80 * -607.50 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-1058.80 * -607.50 = 1058.80 * 607.50 = 643221.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -430.88 - 1101.44 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-430.88 - 1101.44 = -1532.32"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -1923.64 - 8110.60 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-1923.64 - 8110.60 = -10034.24"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 282.03 的平方根？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "√282.03 = 16.79"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -3124.14 / 1192.09 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-3124.14 / 1192.09 = -2.62"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 2666.20 * 110.52 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "2666.20 * 110.52 = 294668.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n当 x = 4.77 时，求函数 y = 86x^97 的值\n\n### Response:", "solution": "y = 86*4.77^97\ny = 86*6.550625430827758e+65\ny = 5.633537870511873e+67\n函数的值为：5.633537870511922e+67"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -7781.42 / -5327.71 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-7781.42 / -5327.71 = 7781.42 / 5327.71 = 1.46"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n求以下数据的平均值：[27, 89, 99, 64, 76, 50, 100, 49]\n\n### Response:", "solution": "27 + 89 + 99 + 64 + 76 + 50 + 100 + 49 = 554\n554 / 8 = 69.25\n平均值为: 69.25"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -4294.20 + 9857.73 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-4294.20 + 9857.73 = 5563.53"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -1214.14 - 1182.21 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-1214.14 - 1182.21 = -2396.35"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 475.47 的 5 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "475.47^5 = 24300521879382.18"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 5078.04 - 8883.67 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "5078.04 - 8883.67 = -3805.63"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -2023.47 - 1907.67 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-2023.47 - 1907.67 = -3931.14"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n解方程 2x + 60 = 0\n\n### Response:", "solution": "2x = -60.0\nx = -60.0 / 2\nx = -30.0\n方程的解为：-30.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 5415.08 / 8305.15 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "5415.08 / 8305.15 = 0.65"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 2356.30 + 9645.15 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "2356.30 + 9645.15 = 12001.45"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 676.46 的 2 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "676.46^2 = 457598.13"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 7076.54 / -2319.93 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "7076.54 / -2319.93 = -3.05"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -101.17 * -8210.19 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-101.17 * -8210.19 = 101.17 * 8210.19 = 830625.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n解方程 -67x + -29 = 0\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-67x = 29.0\nx = 29.0 / -67\nx = -0.43\n方程的解为：-0.43"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 4415.70 - -2186.85 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "4415.70 - -2186.85 = 4415.70 + 2186.85 = 6602.55"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -513.32 的 3 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-513.32^3 = -135258496.87"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 3180.61 - -7868.88 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "3180.61 - -7868.88 = 3180.61 + 7868.88 = 11049.49"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 7157.98 + -8238.21 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "7157.98 + -8238.21 = -1080.23"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 359.19 * -7366.84 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "359.19 * -7366.84 = -2646095.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -809.94 的 2 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-809.94^2 = 656002.8"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -5049.65 / 9032.66 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-5049.65 / 9032.66 = -0.56"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 126.99 的 1 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "126.99^1 = 126.99"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n去年销售额为 28 万元，今年销售额增加了 82%，请计算今年的销售额。\n\n### Response:", "solution": "= 28 * 1.82 = 50.96"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n一个长方形的长为 60 厘米，宽为 21 厘米，请计算其面积。\n\n### Response:", "solution": "60 * 21 = 1260\n面积为 1260 平方厘米"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -7648.20 / -1462.33 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-7648.20 / -1462.33 = 7648.20 / 1462.33 = 5.23"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 5486.28 + -8198.83 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "5486.28 + -8198.83 = -2712.55"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 9628.09 - -9285.90 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "9628.09 - -9285.90 = 9628.09 + 9285.90 = 18913.99"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n当 x = 1.53 时，求函数 y = 15x^63 的值\n\n### Response:", "solution": "y = 15*1.53^63\ny = 15*432075997766.33\ny = 6481139966494.99\n函数的值为：6481139966494.98"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 9096.92 + -4287.79 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "9096.92 + -4287.79 = 4809.13"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 7872.21 / -5143.52 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "7872.21 / -5143.52 = -1.53"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -8408.81 + 5175.48 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-8408.81 + 5175.48 = -3233.33"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 6960.49 + -2479.37 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "6960.49 + -2479.37 = 4481.12"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -7114.90 / 5453.99 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-7114.90 / 5453.99 = -1.3"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 3069.64 + -4540.58 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "3069.64 + -4540.58 = -1470.94"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n求以下数据的平均值：[36, 23, 33, 56, 55, 72, 44]\n\n### Response:", "solution": "36 + 23 + 33 + 56 + 55 + 72 + 44 = 319\n319 / 7 = 45.57\n平均值为: 45.57"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n一个长方形的长为 30 厘米，宽为 44 厘米，请计算其面积。\n\n### Response:", "solution": "30 * 44 = 1320\n面积为 1320 平方厘米"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 7284.02 + -2762.62 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "7284.02 + -2762.62 = 4521.4"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n一个长方形的长为 18 厘米，宽为 34 厘米，请计算其面积。\n\n### Response:", "solution": "18 * 34 = 612\n面积为 612 平方厘米"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n求以下数据的平均值：[26, 41, 56, 79, 81, 5, 76]\n\n### Response:", "solution": "26 + 41 + 56 + 79 + 81 + 5 + 76 = 364\n364 / 7 = 52.0\n平均值为: 52.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -6642.70 + 2293.71 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-6642.70 + 2293.71 = -4348.99"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -2836.04 + -6589.37 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-2836.04 + -6589.37 = -9425.41"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -2782.13 / 72.66 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-2782.13 / 72.66 = -38.29"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 3140.68 + 6112.77 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "3140.68 + 6112.77 = 9253.45"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n某物体的密度为 9 克/立方厘米，体积为 1 立方厘米，请计算该物体的质量。\n\n### Response:", "solution": "9 * 1 = 9\n9 克"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -700.22 / -8699.15 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-700.22 / -8699.15 = 700.22 / 8699.15 = 0.08"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n解方程 -35x + 80 = 0\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-35x = -80.0\nx = -80.0 / -35\nx = 2.29\n方程的解为：2.29"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -413.93 * -3531.49 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-413.93 * -3531.49 = 413.93 * 3531.49 = 1461790.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 941.34 的 2 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "941.34^2 = 886121.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -4845.92 * -9135.70 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-4845.92 * -9135.70 = 4845.92 * 9135.70 = 44270871.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 168.34 的 2 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "168.34^2 = 28338.36"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 8109.51 - 4209.08 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "8109.51 - 4209.08 = 3900.43"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -1163.03 - -9231.14 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-1163.03 - -9231.14 = -1163.03 + 9231.14 = 8068.11"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 7722.38 - 4159.92 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "7722.38 - 4159.92 = 3562.46"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 3815.76 / -6281.84 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "3815.76 / -6281.84 = -0.61"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 9927.99 - -4181.96 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "9927.99 - -4181.96 = 9927.99 + 4181.96 = 14109.95"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 5807.61 的平方根？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "√5807.61 = 76.21"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 4715.32 * -5259.47 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "4715.32 * -5259.47 = -24800084.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 5651.40 - -4831.27 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "5651.40 - -4831.27 = 5651.40 + 4831.27 = 10482.67"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -9194.16 + -5958.91 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-9194.16 + -5958.91 = -15153.07"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 45.65 / 4297.83 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "45.65 / 4297.83 = 0.01"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 9237.51 的平方根？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "√9237.51 = 96.11"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -4701.55 * 8769.06 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-4701.55 * 8769.06 = -41228174.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n解方程 11x + 64 = 0\n\n### Response:", "solution": "11x = -64.0\nx = -64.0 / 11\nx = -5.82\n方程的解为：-5.82"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 5851.95 * 2017.43 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "5851.95 * 2017.43 = 11805899.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 4342.43 + 8332.32 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "4342.43 + 8332.32 = 12674.75"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n解方程 -28x + 91 = 0\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-28x = -91.0\nx = -91.0 / -28\nx = 3.25\n方程的解为：3.25"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 734.05 的平方根？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "√734.05 = 27.09"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -9576.85 / -7526.45 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-9576.85 / -7526.45 = 9576.85 / 7526.45 = 1.27"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 3286.03 * -8033.87 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "3286.03 * -8033.87 = -26399538.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -5462.74 + -8565.38 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-5462.74 + -8565.38 = -14028.12"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 4129.11 - -6919.07 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "4129.11 - -6919.07 = 4129.11 + 6919.07 = 11048.18"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 1437.03 + 2879.42 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "1437.03 + 2879.42 = 4316.45"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 3906.35 * 2271.03 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "3906.35 * 2271.03 = 8871438.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 6911.95 - 5700.39 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "6911.95 - 5700.39 = 1211.56"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 1908.46 + -4882.32 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "1908.46 + -4882.32 = -2973.86"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 3899.33 - 1603.27 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "3899.33 - 1603.27 = 2296.06"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 4917.70 - -3484.94 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "4917.70 - -3484.94 = 4917.70 + 3484.94 = 8402.64"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -570.03 + 2854.20 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-570.03 + 2854.20 = 2284.17"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 9386.28 / 2862.76 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "9386.28 / 2862.76 = 3.28"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n求以下数据的平均值：[29, 21, 47]\n\n### Response:", "solution": "29 + 21 + 47 = 97\n97 / 3 = 32.33\n平均值为: 32.33"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 3190.15 的平方根？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "√3190.15 = 56.48"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 2998.34 * 3471.30 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "2998.34 * 3471.30 = 10408138.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -617.68 * -3365.23 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-617.68 * -3365.23 = 617.68 * 3365.23 = 2078635.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 2012.37 / 1480.07 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "2012.37 / 1480.07 = 1.36"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -453.61 - 8996.39 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-453.61 - 8996.39 = -9450.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -8621.88 / 5012.04 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-8621.88 / 5012.04 = -1.72"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n解方程 31x + 79 = 0\n\n### Response:", "solution": "31x = -79.0\nx = -79.0 / 31\nx = -2.55\n方程的解为：-2.55"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 5401.27 + 3750.03 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "5401.27 + 3750.03 = 9151.3"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 3743.44 + 2044.79 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "3743.44 + 2044.79 = 5788.23"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 561.81 的 3 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "561.81^3 = 177324357.78"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n商品原价为 1 元，打折后的价格为 84 元，请计算打折的折扣比例。\n\n### Response:", "solution": "= (1 - 84) / 1 * 100\n= -83 / 1 * 100\n= -83.0 * 100\n= -8300.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 7132.91 * -2496.53 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "7132.91 * -2496.53 = -17807524.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 5181.89 * 1825.05 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "5181.89 * 1825.05 = 9457208.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n求以下数据的平均值：[12, 28, 21, 86, 56, 96]\n\n### Response:", "solution": "12 + 28 + 21 + 86 + 56 + 96 = 299\n299 / 6 = 49.83\n平均值为: 49.83"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 263.65 的 3 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "263.65^3 = 18326660.18"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -871.47 的 4 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-871.47^4 = 576779432210.23"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 538.10 / 4758.54 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "538.10 / 4758.54 = 0.11"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -3288.38 - 5111.78 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-3288.38 - 5111.78 = -8400.16"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 -979.16 的 5 次方？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "-979.16^5 = -900053485888861.9"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 264.95 的平方根？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "√264.95 = 16.28"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 7233.93 * 5750.17 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "7233.93 * 5750.17 = 41596327.0"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 4363.54 + 8053.97 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "4363.54 + 8053.97 = 12417.51"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 6571.23 的平方根？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "√6571.23 = 81.06"}
{"problem": "Below is an instruction that describes a grade school math problem. Write a response that gives the correct answer.\n\n### Instruction:\n计算 7728.88 * 7531.07 等于多少？\n\n### Response:", "solution": "7728.88 * 7531.07 = 58206736.0"}
